{
    "subject": "resource/Time_(magazine)",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:American_weekly_magazines",
    "human_readable": "Time magazine is about Category:American weekly magazines.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7442327737808228,
            "question": "What type of publication is Time magazine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5938337445259094,
            "question": "How often is Time magazine published?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.528424859046936,
            "question": "What is the main purpose of Time magazine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.50167316198349,
            "question": "What are some notable past covers of Time magazine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4992278814315796,
            "question": "What kind of content does Time magazine typically feature?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4925898313522339,
            "question": "Where is Time magazine based?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3418270945549011,
            "question": "Who are the target readers of Time magazine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32920074462890625,
            "question": "When was Time magazine first published?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.260440856218338,
            "question": "Has Time magazine won any awards for its journalism?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2044130116701126,
            "question": "How has Time magazine adapted to the changing media landscape?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Time magazine is about Category:American weekly magazines.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6644_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Time magazine won any awards for its journalism?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6644_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was Time magazine first published?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6644_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are the target readers of Time magazine?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6644_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6644_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6644_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6644_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6644_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6644_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6644_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6644_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6644_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6644_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6644_84.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple because it is mentioned that TIME Magazine is a weekly news magazine based and printed in New York City (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6644/re-ranker-msmarco/30.txt), which confirms that it is indeed an American weekly magazine."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe information provided in the documents supports the statement that \"Time magazine is about Category:American weekly magazines.\" The documents describe Time Magazine as a weekly news magazine based and printed in New York City, founded in 1923, with a wide circulation in the United States. These details align with its categorization as an American weekly magazine."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}